<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>minutes &#8211; North Carolina Professional Association of Nannies</title>
	<atom:link href="https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/tag/minutes/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/</link>
	<description>Better nannying for North Carolina starts here!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 03:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/wp-content/uploads/cropped-8fc99da8df4a6655108c4061806d6fe69dea0524_l-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>minutes &#8211; North Carolina Professional Association of Nannies</title>
	<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">86020397</site>	<item>
		<title>NC PAN July 2017 Board Meeting: Minutes</title>
		<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48874</link>
					<comments>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48874#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Autumn Racine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 21:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Members Only Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minutes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#160; NCPAN July 2017 Monthly Board Meeting Meeting started at 7:13pm Members Present: Jennifer Levenbook Jennifer Johnson Laura Pearl Jennifer Temple Jasmine Berry Sarah Brady Wagner &#160; Motion: Approve previous meeting’s minutes-everyone does. Officer Reports: Treasurer- NCPAN owes Jennifer Levenbook $2500 and there is less than that in the bank account. Start up costs. All [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe src="http://docdro.id/x1vFjS3" width="800" height="600" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><span id="more-48874"></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">NCPAN July 2017 Monthly Board Meeting</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meeting started at 7:13pm</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Members Present:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jennifer Levenbook</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jennifer Johnson</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Laura Pearl</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jennifer Temple</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jasmine Berry</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sarah Brady Wagner</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Approve previous meeting’s minutes-everyone does.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officer Reports: Treasurer- NCPAN owes Jennifer Levenbook $2500 and there is less than that in the bank account. Start up costs. All other founding loans have been paid back.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Membership- No Greensboro nannies are really interested yet. Need graphics and to give info to Greensboro agencies. Make it clear there are other members besides Jennifer Johnson. Flyers and cards are self-print. Planning a BBQ in Greensboro in September, probably at a park, to invite the Greensboro nannies to. &nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Have Jennifer Johnson look at parks. She agreed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Continuing Officer Reports: Social Chair- Past Events-NNO at the movies, low turnout. People don’t want to go unless it is popular. Paint and Sip will be planned in September. Fridays are better for some than Saturdays. Field Day will be in August. Moana and Wonder Woman are popular NNO movies. August 4</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, playdate at Kidzu (note from minutes taker, I’ll actually be at that one as far as I know!). People with non-napping older kids who want afternoon playdates should host them. </span></p>
<p><b>Action:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Recruit more members with older kids.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Continuing Officer Reports: Professional Development-Going to plan some. (and then talk about ideas later in the meeting) </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a lot of nannies who come to events aren’t NCPAN members. Members get to vote and make decisions but all nannies, member or not, can benefit from the events. Nannies don’t know how to ask for bosses to pay for trainings. Assertiveness Training would help with that. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Continuing Officer Reports: continuing with Treasurer- NNTD fund is in the negative. Can transfer from the swag fund, membership fund, social committee fund, or petty cash. In the black $422.42 overall. NNTD fund is under by $62.15. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> NNTD speakers loved being there. Good variety of topics. Downfall was how long the day was. Air conditioner was broken, that didn’t help. People enjoyed it. Speakers caused the negative money, not enough tickets sold to break even or make money. Written commitment by a sponsor- Nanny By Design- (minutes have been corrected to which agency it was actually) to cover a speaker’s cost was not honored. That sponsor-Nanny By Design- has been blacklisted. They have been slow to pay before, and now they didn’t pay the $400, which would have put NNTD fund in the positive.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> correct the minutes about which sponsor that was from the beginning. Seconded. (minutes are correct from the beginning now)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Blacklist Nanny By Design. All agreed. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion: </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">NCPAN is tired of running NNTD. Next year an agency-My Girl Friday- wants to run it. NCPAN will help if the agency wants it, but not run it. If no one else is going to run it, NCPAN will step up and run it. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Old Business-Field Day- in a yard near a private residence in Carrboro, address available to people RSVPed yes. Area will be given. Alternative could be Oval Park, but they don’t have a bathroom. The private residence yard has bathroom(s) available in the house. A water hookup outside and permission to use all the water needed. Trampoline available. Liability wavers given out. Contests to see who spills the least amount of water. Kiddie pools and an inflatable pool and a sprinkler to play in. &nbsp;NCPAN will provide the watermelon. Bring your own picnic lunch. </span><b>NCPAN will bring toilet paper.</b> <b>Don’t forget.</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Caroline (minutes taker) bold the previous statement. I agree, has been put in bold. I also put Actions in bold, so I made the toilet paper statement bigger print as well. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">of Field Day continued- juice boxes will be provided too. Thinking about the date being August 1</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">st</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, but that’s next week, people might need more time. August 15</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> was decided on. 10am-1pm. Bring swim diapers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to correct the minutes to put Professional Development here and not over there with the Officer Reports. Seconded. (No problem-corrected)</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Professional Development Ideas- Childcare. Probably not CPR. Assertiveness Training. Contracts. Leadership. Financial Literacy. Self-care. Healthcare. Two hour long professional development. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Firehouse Outing. Could go to Chapel Hill, Carrboro, or Durham. Raleigh would be good to get Raleigh nannies interested and Durham was last year. Raleigh area-near the airport. Lots of Raleigh nannies live (or their nanny families live) near the airport. Or Cary. Deciding when and whether to try to include older kids. Tried to plan for Columbus Day but not all schools are off. So it will be toddlers only. Sept 5</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. 10am. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> October will be a Halloween craft. Week of the 23</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">rd</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion: </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Asked Jennifer Temple, Professional Development Officer, to have a proposal of what topic to focus on for professional development by next meeting. She agreed. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> What to for NCPAN going forward. Whether to keep it just playdates and professional development. Wanting to help nannies learn about healthcare. Wanting NCPAN to expand and do more things. Need more local, but non Triangle, affiliates. Need to plan out the guidelines for them. How many playdates and professional developments they will need to do. Clear checklist of what they would need to do to maintain. What each chapter would need to do and where they are. Raleigh nannies could have their own chapter. The board would be the NC board and get the information from each chapter about what they are doing. Each chapter would need a mini board of their own. The NC board will make sure that each chapter is meeting their goals. Also they would help the chapters by networking them a solution to what they are working on. Each chapter would be responsible for a capstone dinner at the end of NNRW. Nannies would go to the chapter in the town/area where they nanny. Chapters could spend their money on their area. Each chapter would pay an affiliation fee to NCPAN. Treasurer could maintain the membership fees and accounts for each chapter to start. If it got big and each chapter had a treasurer there would be measures put in place to keep everything clean and no embezzlement. Each chapter would need a Professional Development Officer and also a Social Chair. Optional Liaison Person. People have to be a member to start their own chapter. Free to start, after a year there will be a $10 fee. Chapters get 90% of membership fees from their chapter to spend on their chapter. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Benefits of being an NCPAN member. Get to vote and help decide things. Free or reduced cost of events. Good to network with other nannies in the area. Helping the nannies of NC become better nannies through professional development classes and networking. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> How to recruit volunteers. Make a personal invitation from a trusted friend. Provide trusted friends with stationery and postage and ask them to hand write a plea to help. Also help them know what to say in the plea. Calling is the next best way, email after that.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discussion:</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Bring in more charity work to show the volunteers the benefits to the community. Also professionally help them learn to work with other people and other skills like event planning. People would work for NCPAN not the charity though.</span></p>
<p><b>Action:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Look at charity options. Plan a Nanny Work Day to benefit the community. Making sure the charity is going to help with professional development. Like holding babies at the hospital to help and learn how to hold babies. Will be discussed more when options are looked into. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amendment Proposal: Have an official code of ethics. Mostly for the board members, because they are the face of NCPAN and we can’t force other members to follow it. Being committed of a crime, misuse of NCPAN’s social media, use of profanity on the social media. All members are not allowed to cyberbully. Board members have special rules. Don’t break the law. Code of conduct is on the NCPAN facebook page. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motion:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Jasmine, email out the proposed code of ethics to the board 10 days before the next meeting. She agreed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meetings will be the 4</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Tuesday of the month. Aim to have in person meeting at least 4 times a year. Rest can be call in.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Next meeting will be August 22</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">nd</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 7pm. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Review of actions: Graphics for memberships. Going to plan a BBQ or NNO in Greensboro in Sept. Going to pick a Paint and Sip for NNO. Moana Aug 11</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and Wonder Woman August 19</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for NNOs. Wear Nanny shirts. Field Day August 15</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 10am-1pm. Firehouse Sept. 5</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Halloween Craft the week of Oct. 23</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">rd</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Figure out what’s in the affiliate package. Email out the proposed code of ethics. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meeting Adjourned at 8:44pm</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Minutes by Caroline Harmon</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48874/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">48874</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NC PAN June 2017 Board Meeting: Minutes</title>
		<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/49372</link>
					<comments>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/49372#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Autumn Racine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 01:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Members Only Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minutes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/49372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-audio"><audio controls src="https://archive.org/download/NannyCast015/25June2017MeetingNcPan.mp3"></audio><figcaption>Audio for the meeting. Transcribed minutes coming.</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/49372/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/NannyCast015/25June2017MeetingNcPan.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg" />

		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">49372</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NC PAN March 2017 Board Meeting: Minutes</title>
		<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48668</link>
					<comments>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48668#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Autumn Racine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 03:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Members Only Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minutes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48668</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NCPAN March 2017 Monthly Board Meeting Meeting started at 7:07pm Members Present: Jenni Levenbook Sarah Brady Jennifer Johnson Jasmine Berry Laura Pearl Discussion about NNTD marketing push Action: need as many nannies as possible Action: keep Triangle nannies from going to Charlotte Action: Committee meeting next week Action: Board members emailing schools Motion: Sarah makes [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe src="https://www.docdroid.net/w61iG40/ncpan-march-2017-monthly-board-meeting.docx.html" width="800" height="600" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><span id="more-48668"></span></p>
<p>NCPAN March 2017 Monthly Board Meeting</p>
<p>Meeting started at 7:07pm</p>
<p>Members Present:</p>
<p>Jenni Levenbook</p>
<p>Sarah Brady</p>
<p>Jennifer Johnson</p>
<p>Jasmine Berry</p>
<p>Laura Pearl</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about NNTD marketing push</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> need as many nannies as possible</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> keep Triangle nannies from going to Charlotte</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> Committee meeting next week</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> Board members emailing schools</p>
<p>Motion: Sarah makes a template and emails preschools-Sarah agrees</p>
<p>Motion: Jennifer Johnson makes a list and emails Greensboro schools-Jennifer agrees</p>
<p>Motion: Laura emails private schools (non public regular schools)-Laura agrees (with help)</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about any new memberships</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> Find out if there are any new memberships (a board member will be emailed when a new member joins)</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about past and future crafts</p>
<p><b>Action: </b>Easter craft is April 14<sup>th&nbsp; </sup>(changed from April 4<sup>th</sup> to be on the same day as the hunt)</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> Easter egg hunt is April 14<sup>th &nbsp;</sup> (in Solite park in Durham)</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about not needing permission to have the hunt at the park</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> Easter egg hunt has two times, 1030 (changed from 1230) for toddlers and 330 for older children</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about timing, who would be able to go.</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about last year’s turnout for morning and afternoon.</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> find a person to run the craft for older kids</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> get older kids to come to the hunt/craft</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about how to make crafts for older kids</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about funds for supplies (confirmed funds)</p>
<p>Motion: get the craft supplies from Aishia -members working on that</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> put the Easter egg hunt info everywhere</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about how people don’t rsvp, how many crafts to make (too many but enough)</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about whether NCPAN has money (yes but needs more NNTD tickets sold, 8 sold so far)</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about tickets sold through My Girl Friday, flyer will be emailed out this week. Unless the agency workers have work or another obligation they are expected to go to NNTD</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> if a board member can’t access their NCPAN email, contact Jenni for a reset</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> board members need to check their emails (can get them forwarded or set up on your phone for easier checking)</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> email the schools from the NCPAN email</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about how to add an email account to a phone</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about getting the board meeting email to regular email addresses, automatic system</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about NNO in March, and there will be one in April</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about the fact that the frost killed the strawberries at the usual farm, so no picking</p>
<p>Motion: Have an NNO in June- all agreed</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> don’t plan anything soon after NNTD</p>
<p><i>Discussion</i> about Nannypalooza, in Maryland in October</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> promote Nannypalooza at NNTD</p>
<p><b>Action:</b> buy Nannypalooza tickets soon, they sold out last year</p>
<p>Meeting Adjourned at 7:37pm</p>
<p>Minutes by Caroline Harmon</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48668/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">48668</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NC PAN January 2017 Board Meeting: Minutes</title>
		<link>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48514</link>
					<comments>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48514#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Autumn Racine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 15:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Members Only Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minutes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/?p=48514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NCPAN January 2017 Monthly Board Meeting Meeting Started at 7:38pm Members Present: 919-428-4393 Jennifer Johnson Laura Pearl Sarah Brady 919-594-4287 Jenni Levenbook Beginning of the meeting was not recorded. Discussion about needing to contact the Raleigh Fire Dept. Discussion about either baby related topic or STEM. Action: Need to contact STEM- to confirm. If not [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe src="https://www.docdroid.net/Cu8fRL2/ncpan-january-2017-monthly-board-meeting-minutes.docx.html" width="800" height="600" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><span id="more-48514"></span></p>
<p>NCPAN January 2017 Monthly Board Meeting</p>
<p>Meeting Started at 7:38pm</p>
<p>Members Present:</p>
<p>919-428-4393</p>
<p>Jennifer Johnson</p>
<p>Laura Pearl</p>
<p>Sarah Brady</p>
<p>919-594-4287</p>
<p>Jenni Levenbook</p>
<p>Beginning of the meeting was not recorded.</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about needing to contact the Raleigh Fire Dept.</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about either baby related topic or STEM.</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Need to contact STEM- to confirm. If not STEM, look into baby-wearing speaker.</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about once speakers are confirmed, people can choose which ones they want to be with when they register.</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Flyers will be made. NNTD committee meeting will be called. Tell all Nannies about NNTD</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about Registration/Ticket Purchase is available, not yet able to pick slots for speakers</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: 5 dollars off if registration is before 11:59PM Thursday 1/19/2017</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Tell all NC nannies on Facebook about NCPAN’s NNTD</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Need someone (possibly Aishia, or former/current board member) to go to LinkedIn and send out a mass email with registration url to all nannies in network</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> of how to find and email nannies on LinkedIn and the importance of keeping track of who was emailed to avoid double-emailing</p>
<p><u>Motion</u>: Sarah will help-Sarah agreed</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about Marketing for NNTD, query for new ideas for 2017</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Flyers, “My Girl Friday” agency will email, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, reached out to Carolina Parent about a Nanny Story, going to reach out to radio and news stations about NNTD, waiting for speakers to confirm. Reach out to Community news (example: The Cary Citizen) and Mother/Childcare Groups too.</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Need more Raleigh groups/marketing because NNTD is in Raleigh</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about having a social in Raleigh before NNTD</p>
<p><u>Motion</u>: Call Laura about NNOs in Raleigh and Cary.-Laura agrees.</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about NNOs, including karaoke</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Fill the calendar with events</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Have more NNOs and crafts and other professional development before NNTD</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: NNOs in Feb and March</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about the website, Jenni Levenbook got it up and running, Bigtent is no longer the one to use.</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em>: 4 tickets sold for NNTD</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Must sell NNTD tickets</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Planning committee for NNTD will receive email about in person meeting</p>
<p><u>Motion</u>: next meeting will be Thursday, Feb 16<sup>th</sup> 730pm-all agreed</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> of how to record meetings</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: Find new secretary</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about Caroline Harmon being a good fit for that</p>
<p><u>Motion</u>: Ask Caroline-all agreed (note: Caroline also accepted the position)</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> about a Triangle Caregivers Meetup organizer stepping down</p>
<p><u>Motion</u>: NCPAN taking over the Meetup-all agreed</p>
<p><em>Discussion</em> of failed meetups for that group at IHOP in Raleigh</p>
<p><strong>Action</strong>: market crafts and events through the Meetup</p>
<p>Meeting Adjourned at 832pm</p>
<p>Minutes by Caroline Harmon</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://theinfamousj.github.io/ncpan/uncategorized/48514/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">48514</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
